https://gallowayridge.com/privacy-policy/

919-328-2657 RESIDENT PORTAL
HomeExploreOur ApartmentsOur VillasFloor PlansServices and AmenitiesFor Your Dining PleasureAround The AreaVirtual TourGalloway Ridge OutdoorsLifeCareThe Benefits of LifeCareThe ArborOn-Site Health Care ServicesDuke Center For LivingDuke Primary CareCenter For Physical RehabilitationLifestyleWellnessLife EnrichmentLibrary Virtual TourA Legacy of VolunteeringGiving BackCommunity EventsArtists CollaborationLearn MoreOur TeamBoard Of DirectorsAnnual ReportFAQsTestimonialsBlogContact UsHomeExploreOur ApartmentsOur VillasFloor PlansServices and AmenitiesFor Your Dining PleasureAround The AreaVirtual TourGalloway Ridge OutdoorsLifeCareThe Benefits of LifeCareThe ArborOn-Site Health Care ServicesDuke Center For LivingDuke Primary CareCenter For Physical RehabilitationLifestyleWellnessLife EnrichmentLibrary Virtual TourA Legacy of VolunteeringGiving BackCommunity EventsArtists CollaborationLearn MoreOur TeamBoard Of DirectorsAnnual ReportFAQsTestimonialsBlogContact Us
Privacy Policy
admin admin
2018-01-03T08:09:55-05:00
Privacy PolicyProtecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Galloway Ridge site. This statement of privacy governs data collection and usage. By using the Galloway Ridge website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
What Does this Statement of Privacy Cover?
This Privacy Policy covers Galloway Ridge’s treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that Galloway Ridge obtains when you access the Sites. It also covers the collection and use of non-personally identifying information such as age, gender and interests. This policy does not cover the practices of other companies or any companies that link to or otherwise refer to the Site.
Collection of your Personal Information
Galloway Ridge may collect Personal Information, such as your name. If you complete a Galloway Ridge online form, we collect the information you provide. This information is used to send information you request via the form, to contact you to provide information requested in the form, and to email information of interest to you about Galloway Ridge. You can opt out of providing this additional information by not providing it when asked to do so. Galloway Ridge may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you for purposes of improving your online experience. Information about your browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the Site, to maintain quality of the Site, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Galloway Ridge website.
Galloway Ridge encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Galloway Ridge so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Galloway Ridge is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Galloway Ridge website.
Use of your Personal Information
Galloway Ridge collects and uses your personal information to operate its websites and deliver the information you have requested. Galloway Ridge may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of news, events or other topics of interest.
Galloway Ridge DOES NOT SELL, RENT or LEASE its CUSTOMER LISTS TO THIRD PARTIES.
Galloway Ridge DOES NOT CONNECT DATA FROM ONE SOURCE TO OTHER DATA WE MAY HAVE ABOUT THE END USER (such as data from forms completed on our Site(s).
Collection of Anonymous Demographic Information
Galloway Ridge has implemented analytics features that gather non-personally identifiable anonymous demographic information from Google Display Advertising and 3rd party audience data such as age, gender and interests. This information is not unique to you and cannot identify you personally in any way.
Use of Anonymous Demographic
Galloway Ridge uses non-personally identifiable information IN AGGREGATE in order to deliver information of interest to our visitors more efficiently. The use of this anonymous demographic information is limited to improving your online experience with our Site(s).
Use of Cookies
The Galloway Ridge website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you complete a form on the Site, a cookie helps Galloway Ridge to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information. When you return to the same Galloway Ridge website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Galloway Ridge site.
Security of your Personal Information
Galloway Ridge secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We routinely scan our source code to check for weaknesses or vulnerabilities. When personal information is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
Children Under Thirteen
Galloway Ridge does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Galloway Ridge by contacting us here:
By Phone:919-328-2657
Online: https://gallowayridge.com/contact-us/
To opt out of Google services:https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/
You may also change your Ads Settings within your Google account to help control the types of Google ads you see, and the information gathered therefrom here.
Galloway Ridge Retirement Community
3000 Galloway Ridge Road
Pittsboro, NC 27312
We’re happy to provide you
with more information. Check out
our tools or contact us
for more informationCost CalculatorPersonalized
BrochureContact Us
Phone NumberDescriptionEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
X
Schedule a Tour
First Name*Last Name*Email*
Phone NumberDescriptionCommentsThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
X
